# Noah J. Holt

Email: noahjmholt@gmail.com Willing to Relocate: Negotiable

Cell: 803.468.3236 Willing to Travel: Yes

**Security Clearance:** Able to Obtain

#### **EXPERIENCE SUMMARY**

Pursuing a full-time career in Computer Science. Wanting to explore the field of computer science and reach my niche. Interests I have found in the field include app development, security, networks, and data science. Though I have explored these fields, I feel I have barely scratched their surfaces leaving curiosity and interests to explore.

Goal and results oriented communicator, training, and ability to work well in highly stressful situations and environments. One year of education based IT troubleshooting and assistance, with an extra 2+ years of customer service and relationship building experience.

### **EDUCATION**

University of Colorado-Colorado Springs: Bachelor's in Computer Science, May 2024

PIMA Medical Institute: Associates of Veterinary Technology, May 2020

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

CompTIA A+, Cert #: COMP001022097585 Notary Public, ID 20254005965

## SUMMARY OF SKILLS, TOOLS, AND TECHNOLOGIES:

Java, C, C#, C++, R, Python	Object Oriented Programming Knowledge	Microsoft Office Suites
Docker and AWS	Agile frameworks	Trainer & Education
Git and GitHub	Windows and Linux Operating System	Rugby Coach
WordPress, Django, TypeScript	IT Service Desk (Tier 1 and Tier 2)	CPR & BLS

Bash Scripting Hardware/Computer building

# PROJECT WORK EXPERIENCE

## Secret Santa Wish List, Class Project: Sep 2023 – Dec 2023

Created wish list Web app for users to login, add items viewable the public.

- Implemented CRUD application with one-to-many relationship for database.
- Using an agile workflow, Django for web development, docker for storage and AWS for hosting

#### EXPERIENCE DETAILS

# Clawson & Clawson LLP - Legal Assistant/Admin: Nov 2024 - Current

- Assist Attorneys and Paralegals in day-to-day tasks such as intensive customer service in person and over the phone, bookkeeping and records keeping, new client onboarding, and scheduling tasks.
- Helped facilitate migration to new software thru employee training, manual data entry, and communications with company to make sure things moved smoothly.

## UCCS OIT – IT Technician: Mar 2022 – Nov 2023

- Provided Tier 1 and 2 technical support, as dedicated Help Desk professional providing technical support in a 15,000+ student and 1,000+ faculty user environment.
- Problem-solver that can communicate with users at all levels of technical proficiency.
- Troubleshoot, resolve, and document user help requests for desktop, laptop, mobile, network and peripheral problems. Platforms include Windows, Mac OS X, iOS, Chrome OS, Android.
- Imaging, configuring, and managing of MacOS and Windows machines.
- Troubleshooting: networking, secure VPN, operating systems (iOS, Windows), and printers.
- Maintaining and monitoring 1,000+ machines across campus area network.
- Responsible for teaching/assisting new employees in their daily routines, evaluated performances, critiqued knowledge and performance, and conducted individual assistance.
- Remote administration responsibilities for software and hardware installation across the Campus Area Network, in direct support of students/faulty/staff, and devices.
- Field and implemented intranet and enterprise security policies for the UCCS network infrastructure.

## Scheels All Sport, Colorado Springs – Service Shop Technician: Jan 2021 – Feb 2022

• Provided assistance and instructions to customers and fellow associates in maintenance of various products, while providing world class customer service.

## Colorado Canine Orthopedics and Rehab – Vet Tech, Technician: Jun 2019 – Mar 2020

Responsible for performing routine checkups and other medical procedures on animals to
ensure their health and well-being. These requirements included communicating with pet
parents to determine whether their pet experienced changes in activity or diet, checking an
animal's weight, heartbeat, and other vital signs to record in patient files, and assisting other
veterinary personnel in taking blood samples or administering medications.

#### Links:

https://github.com/NoahjmHolt

https://www.linkedin.com/in/noah-holt-23560522b/